CURRICULUM VITAE

WAODE MAKANI DAGA

Phone Number: +6281341686169

Email: dagawaodemakani@gmail.com

Name : Waode Makani Daga Place of Birth : Gowa, South Sulawesi

Date of Birth : 29 October 1993

Address : Sapiria

RT/RW 002/006 Benteng Somba Opu

Barombong, Gowa

Sex : Female

Height/Weight : 155 cm / 65 kg

Marital Status : Single
Religion : Islam
Nationality : Indonesia

SUMMARY

Database Administrator with +1 years of experience based on project team which focuses on the completion of the business flow in an event organizer that is implemented in the database architecture in the information system.

Java Programmer based on *Object Oriented Programming (OOP)* in a few months to development of information systems applications.

SKILLS

- Linux Operation
- Database development (MYSQL)
- Object Oriented Programming (OOP)

EXPERIENCE

UI DESIGNERNov 2015 – Apr 2016TAMAN SURYA SPORT CLUB (TSSC)West Jakarta

- Build user interface architecture on information systems using Photoshop CS4 Application.
- Develop database architecture with developers in point of sales application.



DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR SKYPION PROJECT

Nov 2016 – Sep 2017 South Sulawesi

- Build database architecture to follow the business flow on an event organizer project.
- Develop the process flow from each table in the database using MYSQL.

Jr. JAVA PROGRAMMER SKYPION PROJECT

Oct 2017 – Feb 2018

South Sulawesi

Develop an Event Organizer application program based on Information System using Java Programming language.

EDUCATION

FΟ	RM	\mathbf{AL}

BACHELOR'S DEGREE: INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY
STMIK KHARISMA MAKASSAR
South Sulawesi

HIGH SCHOOL : SCIENCE MAJOR

SMA SATRIA MAKASSAR

South Sulawesi

JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL 2006 – 2009 SMP SATRIA MAKASSAR South Sulawesi

PRIMARY SCHOOL 2000 – 2006
SD INPRES MACCINI BARU South Sulawesi

KINDERGARTEN 1998 – 2000 TK KEMALA BHAYANGKARI South Sulawesi

NON FORMAL

AL KHAWARIZMY
2012 – 2016
STMIK KHARISMA MAKASSAR
South Sulawesi

INSTITUT KARATE-DO NASIONAL 2007 – 2013 MAKASSAR South Sulawesi

COMPUTER OPERATOR 2012

PUSAT PENDIDIKAN KOMPUTER KHARISMA South Sulawesi

ENGLISH COURSE 2010 – 2011
VEEFA INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE South Sulawesi

KLUB JANTUNG SEHAT REMAJA 2010

MAKASSAR South Sulawesi